Joshua Loysch

FULL STACK DEVELOPER, AUDIO ENGINEER

Rochester, NY | 570.280.5960 | joshualoysch@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/jloysch | https://jloysch.github.io

SUMMARY

Full Stack Developer with 6+ years of experience developing applications implementing a wide variety of solutions. Equipped with strong knowledge of data structures, algorithms, and good coding practices. Seeking to leverage knowledge toward career growth.

Expertise Includes:

iOS/Android Development | Full Stack Development | UI/UX | Audio Engineering | Communications

WORK EXPERIENCE

GrubHub, DoorDash - Rochester, New York

Delivery Partner, 2022 - Present

Regularly completing a high volume of deliveries while maintaining clear and concise communication with all parties involved.

- Constant self-reflection on methodology reducing average delivery times by 16%
- Comfortable maintaining temperament in stressful circumstances

Candlelight Bar & Grille - Union Dale, Pennsylvania

Server, Sous-Chef, Dishwasher (Summer), 2019

Worked as a dishwasher occasionally performing sous-chef, bartender, or server duties as needed.

- · Gained great customer service experience through actively performing my duties in a front facing capacity
- Attained extremely keen attention to detail through numerous years of 'finish-work' (painting, drywalling, flooring, and more)

Forest City Nursing and Rehab Center - Forest City, Pennsylvania

Dietary Aide, Sous-Chef, 2017 - 2020

Having knowledge of regular diets, therapeutic diets, fluid consistencies, texture manipulation, and much more, my duties pertained mainly to the planning and execution of the care plans assigned to residents at the nursing home.

- HIPAA and ServSafe certification attained
- · Must quickly implement resident-specific modifications on a case-by-case basis with precision and haste

 $Independent-Scranton,\,Pennsylvania$

Skilled Laborer (Seasonal), 2014 - 2022

Worked as a laborer performing a wide variety of skilled tasks to transform the vision of the customer into reality.

- · Worked exclusively in small teams with the utmost accountability to get the job done properly and in time
- Attained extremely keen attention to detail through numerous years of 'finish-work' (painting, drywalling, flooring, and more)

Audio Engineer, 2014 – Present

Engaged in all aspects of audio engineering from music production to troubleshooting hardware to so much more.

- Professional experience and mastery of many DAWS, plugins, hardware
- Production from all aspects; mixing, recording, songwriting, and much more

EDUCATION

University of Rochester – B.Sc. Computer Science (2023)

With just over 4500 undergraduates, Rochester is one of the smallest and most collegiate in character among the nation's top research universities.

- Received Xerox Award for Innovation in Technology (2019)
- Computer Science Undergraduate Council (CSUG)